Guide to the Zales N. Ecton Papers 1947-1953
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- Photographs, Series 17
  This series includes several photographs of Ecton, members of congress, and other events during Ecton's service as a federal senator. The last file contains some information regarding some of the photographs.
  - #1-9 (Box-folder 34/1)
  - #10-20 (Box-folder 34/2)
  - #21-31 (Box-folder 34/3)
    Photograph #22 removed and placed in oversize folder (enlarged picture of Ecton).
  - Letters Regarding Photographs (Box-folder 34/4)
- Scrapbook Collection, Series 18
  This series contains one binder with congressional records for the 1st session of the 81st Congress and eight scrapbooks pertaining to Ecton and his service as a federal senator. Generally, the scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings linked to Ecton or other governmental issues during his time as a senator.
  - Binder (Box 35)
  - Scrapbook collection, 1-8 (Box 36)